EDUCATION

FSc(Pre-Medical) 2018- 2020 LAHORE BOARD

CONTACT

Susuhme200@gmail.com

PRTOFOLIO:

- https://drive.google.com/d rive/folders/13ii6JPSSbo5 EHpAVr7MVB9oXE8-I9YDK?usp=drive_link
- Scoopwoords.com
- 6itrade.com
- Aroundme.co.in
- tpswatertechnologies.com .pk
- wirasat.com
- · hostingcharges.in

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Seo Content Writer
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Urdu (Native)

SUSHMEELA

CONTENT WRITER

ABOUT ME:

I'm a four-year experienced content writer with a knack for turning complex ideas into engaging, informative pieces. I excel at understanding your brand voice and target audience and crafting content that resonates and drives results.

I create high-quality content across various formats, including blog posts, website copy, social media content, etc. I ensure your content ranks well in search engines by incorporating relevant keywords and crafting a user-friendly experience. I weave compelling narratives that capture attention and keep readers hooked. I analyze content performance and audience insights to refine your content strategy for continuous improvement. I can adapt my writing style to suit diverse audiences and content types. I deliver high-quality work on time, every time. I conduct thorough research to ensure your content is accurate and insightful. I enjoy working closely with clients to understand their needs and deliver content that exceeds expectations.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fiverr:

Content Writer

MAY 2020-OCT 2022

- Worked with internal and external partners to develop and execute content
- strategies. performed well with project requirements and deadlines.
- Created well-researched and stimulating content.
- Worked collaboratively with team members to meet and exceed project goals.

Twine

Content Writer

Dec 2022- Apr 2023

- Researched and created interesting content for a variety of social media platforms.
- Worked one-on-one with clients to understand their content needs and goals.
- Developed content strategies to ensure desirable outcomes.
- · Wrote informative, motivational, and creative articles.
- Created content that accurately reflected company ideals and offerings.

Trcikno-Soft

Aug 2023- Jan 2024

Content Writer

- Thoroughly researched te keywords and craft a compelling article and blogs which SEO based
- Here I wrote article on a diverse range of niches from tech to affiliate or biographies to finance etc.

Freelance Writing Service

June 2024-Present

- I am working as a content and copywriter with various business and freelance clients through LinkedIn.
- I create social media copies, articles, and blog writing on various niches(tech, finance, sport, news, review, AI, informative, biographies, education, health, UX writing, and many more)
- Write posts for social media including ----LinkedIn, and Facebook
- Write YouTube scripts and many more......

EDUCATION

FSc(Pre-Medical) 2018-2020 LAHORE BOARD

CONTACT

• Susuhme200@gmail.com

PRTOFOLIO:

- https://drive.google.com/d rive/folders/13ii6JPSSbo5 EHpAVr7MVB9oXE8-I9YDK?usp=drive_link
- Scoopwoords.com
- 6itrade.com
- Aroundme.co.in
- tpswatertechnologies.com .pk
- · wirasat.com
- · hostingcharges.in

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Seo Content Writer
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Urdu (Native)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wirasat

JULY 2024-DEC 2024

Content Writer

 Collaborate with the SEO expert and developer and create highly engaging blogs, website articles and copies.

Hosting Charges Content Writer

Aug 2024- Nov 2024

 I worked here as a technical writer on a project basis, where i thoroughly research about the keyword first and create the engaging, SEO optimized content while meeting their deadlines